[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 5, "question": "Who is going to blink first?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "going", "to", "blink", "first", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 6, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "Is it conceivable that we could get to August the 2nd and a default happens?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "conceivable", "that", "we", "could", "get", "to", "August", "the", "2nd", "and", "a", "default", "happens", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "It is definitely conceivable.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "definitely", "conceivable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["August"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Can you envisage that kind of scenario?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "envisage", "that", "kind", "of", "scenario", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Yes, I mean, Kate Bolduan, let me go to you, because while President Obama was putting his arm around John Boehner and saying, hey, we're great pals, John Boehner was pretty quick to say, get your hands off me, buddy, wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "Kate", "Bolduan", ",", "let", "me", "go", "to", "you", ",", "because", "while", "President", "Obama", "was", "putting", "his", "arm", "around", "John", "Boehner", "and", "saying", ",", "hey", ",", "we", "'re", "great", "pals", ",", "John", "Boehner", "was", "pretty", "quick", "to", "say", ",", "get", "your", "hands", "off", "me", ",", "buddy", ",", "was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate Bolduan", "Obama", "John Boehner", "John Boehner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "VBN", "VBN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "What did they really mean?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "they", "really", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "Well, Piers, had these speeches been given three or four weeks ago, I think they would have been welcome as part of the political discourse.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "had", "these", "speeches", "been", "given", "three", "or", "four", "weeks", "ago", ",", "I", "think", "they", "would", "have", "been", "welcome", "as", "part", "of", "the", "political", "discourse", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "Has anyone come away better than they did half an hour ago?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "anyone", "come", "away", "better", "than", "they", "did", "half", "an", "hour", "ago", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "I think probably each fellow came off better in his base.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "probably", "each", "fellow", "came", "off", "better", "in", "his", "base", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Boehner"]}, "docId": "110725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VB", "VBZ", "NN", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Can such an intransigent position be helpful to the Republicans right now?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "such", "an", "intransigent", "position", "be", "helpful", "to", "the", "Republicans", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NNPS", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Well, I think there is no doubt that if had just been John Boehner and let's stay the more established Republican leadership, a deal would have been struck.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "there", "is", "no", "doubt", "that", "if", "had", "just", "been", "John", "Boehner", "and", "let", "'s", "stay", "the", "more", "established", "Republican", "leadership", ",", "a", "deal", "would", "have", "been", "struck", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Is it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Well, Piers, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "What did he make of his golfing partner's comments?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "he", "make", "of", "his", "golfing", "partner", "'s", "comments", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Well, I actually -- we were walking out of the room.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "actually", "--", "we", "were", "walking", "out", "of", "the", "room", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "Is the president prepared to invoke the 14th Amendment and unilaterally raise the debt and simply overrule everyone and go alone?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "the", "president", "prepared", "to", "invoke", "the", "14th", "Amendment", "and", "unilaterally", "raise", "the", "debt", "and", "simply", "overrule", "everyone", "and", "go", "alone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Listen, there are no off-ramps here.", "answer_tokens": ["Listen", ",", "there", "are", "no", "off-ramps", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "What does the president do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "the", "president", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Well, listen, we're going to keep making the case, privately and publicly, that compromise is the only option here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "listen", ",", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "keep", "making", "the", "case", ",", "privately", "and", "publicly", ",", "that", "compromise", "is", "the", "only", "option", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "Would you encourage the president to take that option, if all else failed?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "encourage", "the", "president", "to", "take", "that", "option", ",", "if", "all", "else", "failed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PDT", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "Well, I think we ought to avoid that option if we could.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "we", "ought", "to", "avoid", "that", "option", "if", "we", "could", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Schumer"]}, "docId": "110725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "What more do they want?", "question_tokens": ["What", "more", "do", "they", "want", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJR", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Senator Schumer, thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["Senator", "Schumer", ",", "thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "Isn't it time you guys took one for the team, the team being America?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "it", "time", "you", "guys", "took", "one", "for", "the", "team", ",", "the", "team", "being", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Well, if the team is America, the issue is how to get this economy moving again.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "the", "team", "is", "America", ",", "the", "issue", "is", "how", "to", "get", "this", "economy", "moving", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "He had a point, didn't he, the president, raising that quote?", "question_tokens": ["He", "had", "a", "point", ",", "did", "n't", "he", ",", "the", "president", ",", "raising", "that", "quote", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "He did.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Are you guys prepared to compromise, as the president asked, and get the deal done?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "guys", "prepared", "to", "compromise", ",", "as", "the", "president", "asked", ",", "and", "get", "the", "deal", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "Again, I think it's happening.", "answer_tokens": ["Again", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "happening", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "You don't want that, do you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "want", "that", ",", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "Well, I'm opposed to the idea of going bankrupt or hitting the debt ceiling.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "opposed", "to", "the", "idea", "of", "going", "bankrupt", "or", "hitting", "the", "debt", "ceiling", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["six trillion dollars"]}, "docId": "110725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNPS", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Who is it going to be?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "it", "going", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Well, look, the Republicans would like six trillion dollars in spending restraint over the next ten years.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", ",", "the", "Republicans", "would", "like", "six", "trillion", "dollars", "in", "spending", "restraint", "over", "the", "next", "ten", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]